profitswami.com 2016-10-13

# Profit Swami » Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Policy_**

Your privacy is important to Profit Swami LLC (“Profit Swami”). This Privacy Policy describes the information practices for the Profit Swami websites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. As described below, this statement applies to your interactions with the Profit Swami sites as well as other interactions with Profit Swami, such as when you enter into Terms of Use for a Profit Swami offering, or provide information to Profit Swami.

**What Information We Collect:** This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected by or submitted to the Profit Swami (or carefully selected third parties acting on our behalf), including personal information. “Personal information” is data that reasonably can be used to identify or describe an individual. You do not need to provide us personal information to simply browse our site.

**Profit Swami may collect personal information when:**

  * you make purchases of products or services;
  * you request support for a Profit Swami product or service;
  * you register for webcasts, seminars, courses, or other events;
  * you request information or materials;
  * you participate in surveys and evaluations;
  * you participate in promotions, contests, or giveaways;
  * you apply for a job, or submit your resume to Profit Swami;
  * you submit any such information to Profit Swami; or
  * you submit questions or comments to Profit Swami.

Profit Swami may also collect personal information from individuals (with their consent) at conventions, trainings, courses, and other events.

**The types of personal information collected may include (but are not limited to):**

  * your first and last name;
  * your home, billing, or other physical address (including street name, city/town, state/province, postal code);
  * your e-mail address;
  * your telephone number;
  * (for job applicants submitting electronic information) your educational background, employment experience, and job interest;
  * any other identifier that permits Profit Swami to make physical or online contact with you; and
  * your credit card account information.

**Use of Your Personal Information:** Profit Swami collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its sites and deliver the services or carry out the transactions you have requested. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the sites or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services, and technologies; and displaying content and advertising that are customized to your interests and preferences.

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing information, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. Some Profit Swami services may send periodic member letters that are considered part of the service. We may also contact you to inform you of other products or services available from Profit Swami and its affiliates.

Personal information collected on the Profit Swami sites may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Profit Swami or its affiliates, subsidiaries, or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Profit Swami sites or services, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

**Sharing of Your Personal Information:** Profit Swami will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to others. Profit Swami shares personal information with companies working on our behalf. Except as described in this statement, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties for their own marketing purposes unless you have provided consent.

Some Profit Swami services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you register for or use such services, both Profit Swami and the other company may receive information collected as part of the co-branded services. If so, the privacy policy of such other company shall apply to their use of this information.

In some cases Profit Swami uses contractors to collect, use, analyze, and otherwise process information on its behalf. It is Profit Swami’s practice to require such suppliers to handle information in a manner consistent with Profit Swami’s policies. Profit Swami may also team up with carefully selected Profit Swami partners to participate in limited marketing campaigns solely to promote Profit Swami’s products and services, or the partner’s products and services, to you. You may opt-out of receiving these marketing messages at any time by following the instructions in the e-mail message.

If you request something from the Profit Swami site (for example, a product or service, a callback, or specific marketing materials), we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request. To help us do this, we may share information with others, such as Profit Swami’s business partners, financial institutions, shipping companies, and postal or government authorities (e.g., customs authorities) involved in fulfillment. As part of a transaction, we may also contact you as part of our customer satisfaction surveys or for market research purposes.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. Such companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

We may access or disclose your personal information if we believe such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Profit Swami; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Profit Swami (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Profit Swami services or members of the public.

**Your Choices:** Profit Swami provides a number of ways for you to “opt-out” of receiving additional information from us, or having us provide your personal information to our partners. We may offer you these choices at the time you give us your information.

If you do not wish to continue receiving certain marketing materials (e.g., e-mail messages), you can opt-out of receiving these materials by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the materials. This option does not apply to communications primarily for the purpose of administering orders, contracts, support, product safety warnings, software updates, or other administrative and transactional notices.

**How to Update Your Information** : Here are some ways you can modify the contact information that you have provided to us:

  * Email: Should your email address change, you may manage your subscription by unsubscribing to our newsletter and re-subscribing with your new email address.
  * Other personal information: you may update your telephone number or mailing address with us by mailing us at 11 Nod Hill Road, Newton, MA 02461.

**Safeguarding Your Personal Information** : We recognize industry standards and employ security safeguards to protect information from unauthorized access and misuse. We use the most accurate and current information you provide in order to process your request. Furthermore, whenever you transmit sensitive information, such as credit card information, to us through our website, we provide you access to a third party server that allows encryption across the Internet. Browsers offer varying degrees of security, particularly in regard to encryption. Even the same version of a browser can come with different levels of encryption. For your protection, make sure your browser is set and configured to support Secure Socket Layer (SSL) 2.0/3.0 and employs 128-bit encryption. All acceptable browsers do provide detailed information on security levels in “Properties” or “Document Information” from the browser’s menu bar. See your browser’s “Help” tab or documentation for more information.

**Enforcement** : Profit Swami regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this statement or Profit Swami’s treatment of personal information by contacting us at the link or address indicated below.

**Cookies and Browser Information:** Profit Swami uses cookies for a variety of purposes. A “cookie” is a name for tokens of information that our website may provide to your browser while you are at the site. We use cookies to help us keep track of the items that you place in your shopping cart or to better understand website usage in the aggregate so that we know what areas of the Profit Swami sites users prefer. If you simply want to browse, you do not have to accept cookies from the Profit Swami sites. Should you decide, however, that you would like to register for a course or event with Profit Swami and you have modified your browser settings not to accept cookies, you will need to re-set your browser to accept the cookies that we send it. Otherwise, you may not be able to register. Most browsers are defaulted to accept and maintain cookies. These cookies are not tied to your personally identifiable information.

Third party vendors, including Google, may use cookies to serve ads to you while you are using the Profit Swami sites based on your prior visits. You may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

With or without cookies, our website keeps track of usage data, such as the source address from which a page request originates (i.e., your IP address, domain name), date and time of the page request, the referring website (if any), and other parameters in the URL (e.g., search criteria). We use this data to better understand website usage in the aggregate so that we know what areas of our website users prefer (e.g., based on the number of visits to those areas). This information is stored in log files and is used for aggregated and statistical reporting. It is not attributed to you as an individual.

**Links to Other Sites:** The Profit Swami sites may provide links to third-party websites, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers. You should review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why, and how they collect and use personally identifiable information.

**For Questions or Concerns:** If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact amit@profitswami.com. The Profit Swami corporate headquarters are located at:

Profit Swami LLC  
11 Nod Hill Road  
Newton, MA 0246

**Changes to the Profit Swami Privacy Statement** : Profit Swami reserves the right to change this policy from time to time. If we do make changes, the revised Privacy Policy will be posted on this site.

**NOTICE TO CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 18 AND THEIR PARENTS OR LEGAL GUARDIANS** : THE PROFIT SWAMI SITES ARE INTENDED FOR ADULTS. WE DO NOT KNOWINGLY OR INTENTIONALLY COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM ANYONE UNDER THE AGE OF 18. IF YOU ARE UNDER THE AGE OF 18, PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO PROFIT SWAMI. IF YOU KNOW OF ANYONE UNDER THE AGE OF 18 WHO HAS PROVIDED US WITH INFORMATION, PLEASE CONTACT US IMMEDIATELY AND WE WILL REMOVE THE INFORMATION.

_This Privacy Policy was last amended on July 7, 2015._
